MULYADI

+62 838 1123 8370 \$\infty\$ Kab.Tangerang, Banten, 15570 mulyadiseh123@gmail.com \$\infty\$ LinkedIn/Mulyadi

SUMMARY

I am a highly motivated student in UI/UX Design, Graphic Design and Video Editing. With experience in designing for mobile and web app. I also have expertise in web development to create websites and simple programming. In addition, I can edit a video and photos to create interesting content. I have teamwork skills. I am very interested in a career as a UI/UX Design expert.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Informatics, Sultan Ageng Tirtayasa Univesity

(2021- Present)

GPA: 3.83/4.00

- Create a website display design that is in accordance with the web objectives by collaborating with the front end developer team.
- Volunteer in organizing "The 3rd International Conference on Informatics Electricals and Electronics (ICIEE)", a prestigious international conference in that field.
- Member of the Student Association involved in the development and literacy aimed at increasing understanding and skills in the field of information technology.

Social Studies Department, SMAN 20 Kab. Tangerang

2018-2021 (Expeted)

- Head of Civic Education Department (Intra School Student Organization) 2 Priode.
- District level garuda scouts
- 2nd place in Miniature Competition (Naval shipping)

EXPERIENCE

International Conference IEEE

(Feb 2022 - Dec 2022)

Volunteer

- Searching for data on paper makers from various campuses as individual data and finalizing all data in excel.
- Being an operator at the event both offline and online (Zoom) and maintaining the conduciveness of the event.
- Re-typing papers in Latex to tidy up the display from before

ORGANIZATION

UNTIRTA Informatics Student Association

(Nov 2022 - Present)

Research and development division

- Actively engage in meeting sessions aimed at developing in-depth understanding and enhancing skills in the information technology domain.
- Take an active role in an intense collaborative process with the core management to design, build, and improve the organizational structure to achieve the most optimal conditions in all aspects.
- Being part of the management of the web development field for the benefit of HIMA information

Intra-school Student Organization

(2019 - 2021)

Department of Defense Education

- Conducting routine exercises for each class to prepare them for the ceremony every Monday.
- Implementing work programs related to state defense such as youth oath and other days.
- Carry out obligations for every school event and event related to independence day or the country.

SKILLS AND COMPENTIONS

Hard Skill

- Adobe Creative Suit
- Prototype Figma
- UX Principle
- User Research
- Wireframing
- Typography

Soft Skill

- Creativity
- Good communication
- Collaboration
- User Awareness
- Problem solving
- Time Management